I don't care about the people who say I'm a [ __ ] on the internet, I'm a
good walker, I'll confront you about what you tell me right now.
He is Coffee once the Bai Gua news spread the trial he has been in his
career to zero, but did not expect to fall
.  Someone came to me and said eh, I might as well join you,
so I put on his pajamas, then he told me, you must
not waste the influence, I finished you
buy the whole site of pajamas after that.  From the teacher of Shangga family to open.
Hello everyone.  The number of subscribers rushed to 1.8 million yuan, so the flow of
cash flow After opening YouTube, I think the
wealth of this gave me ten dollars back.  Fight 10 times, is lucky
, just sister-in-law, or not as simple as you think.  I
really don't know how many times I have booked this street.
When I first bought something, you posted the blank
drawing 12 times now.  Call one by one, go one by one
money yeah, you do business, in fact, you will.  [Laughter]
We are a YouTube
channel, now it's 900,000,
so I'm a YouTuber, but I
'm this one, he claims he's not one, but his
already 1.8 million, is our double,
so there are many different stomachs, you're also a
teacher, followed by the brand's founders
Road's mother, she is Coffee.  Hello everyone.
Feed, don't be so humble.  The most important thing about you just now is
not, it's the view.  Your
views are so much, you should be very cheap of yourself
refuel is refuel ah, place thank you e encouragement.  I'm angry.  Wow
, what happened?  Is it a movie?  What I would be curious about is that you are actually a
new one, in fact, you have done a lot of different things over the past ten years
, I wonder why you don't consider yourself a
youtuber?  It's 100 or 20 million
.  Actually I want to say I never considered a YouTube
as a job, should ask me if, I think I am
not, so I am a gamma teacher.  You mean you were
teaching gamma while working at the TV station, I don't know? Uh,
I didn't have it when I was at the TV station, that's when I thought
I got a license, why?  Because at that time I was very
lonely, I felt feed me a license, although I used this
money, but in the future I teach myself I do not have to go out and let
others make my money, I think so, my thinking
, so follow me, but at that time I felt that I was still
an actor, I am not you thinking of leaving this industry, I
just really, but how do you know it is a hobby
Unfortunately, I was told off like this, so I found out,
eh no, maybe I have to draw back this one, itself I
'm interested in things, I really have to implement it, so I started to become
a teacher.  Why did I start
YouTube
?  The main income yeah
so I would tell them actually really not, because the oil head
to the end, I did not think of using this thing to make money, just like
my videos, that is some sports videos yeah, I never put in the middle
.  It's not a big struggle. Have you really considered it carefully? It's still
not much.  Actually, actually, I used to have this, that is,
direct-entry advertising, but this to
a point, is I feel very uncomfortable.  why?  I do
n’t know, really I think I think of YouTube
as a home, which means you think of it as a me and my d
, a channel for communication, and I take classes with them there
, I come into contact with them there, I always feel
like I’m there to eat, I won’t be there.  I'm OK?I was
trying to karma your own very personal
thing.  Yeah, and I think when my interest, my
happiness, becomes something very disgusting, I don't want to
appear there anymore, so I think it's a very
short thing, so but for me yes, yes, at this
moment you think a lot of money, but the next second you actually
feel like actually because of this one money you lost a more
detailed person, so you will respect more
As for me, I would make a clear distinction that I would
think that it was where I made people like me that I would continue to be
there, or somewhere else that I would be able to use for advertising
.  OK? Morning.  early.  Yes.  But my own place
pays my own place so, I have this one belief.
Well, although you don't consider YouTube as anything, that
is, a business, you consider it as a sharing
, but how much do you think it has brought you, that is,
on your four pages.  Wow, I want to say actually I didn't really consider the
YouTube as a place to make money, but I
think I started after I opened it, I think the wealth of this gave
my life maybe ten 100
YouTube gave me, not
YouTube.  Directly from YouTube
.  Not something directly on YouTube
, I think it is so strong, but all my
followers this is brought over on my
YouTube to now,
they are very big, because of my followers, they are
thinking that I will believe whatever coffeeeffe says,
I do whatever, that is, go to that, so and I will not
betray them.  Yeah.  Yes I will not mess around like this,
today tell you this cream is good, tomorrow tell you
this cream is good, I never will, I am
very conscientious to do this, because I think money is not
earned, that is, I will not be like this to go out of my
followers, because I know they are my
family, I took them as their family to go
.  So so I think this is why they have
followed me for so many years?  That is why do some people think
my follow is so valuable, why do they think it
is so valuable because of that?  You were actually eh
before covid, actually was already releasing your gamma
video, so it was against him when some people were at home that was not released
, was there a very obvious rise at that time
.  There was cug at that time, and exaggerated.  I actually this
I want to say really star this not that was before covid c pre-
c I think at that time, I remember it was a video, it was about
doing, it was teaching everyone how to practice very simply.  So
my video is my first 1 million, 10,000 views
video came so then this slowly more people on
the street to tell me it, a lot of rise during that time I rose the
fastest so at that time I think I was probably around 300,000
, so I went to rise to 1 million when I think it would be within two years
.  Good ffee you go start something
because actually you start anything is not
simple, you have to teach it, then to teach
YouTubechannel, you are the kind of
done first, and then slowly good, or
actually do before I have to be very good first this part of this part, and
then this second month 3rd month I have to have a
roadmap to see
when this is the kind of you are the one.  After thinking I will think a lot of failed things first
, that is, I will not question myself first.  So but when I grow up
I think it's experienced more, that is, you failed
, so you find it feed, actually nothing
tolose right this world, in fact, you can be at worst so right
so, you can no longer be worse there is nothing for
me to lose over right so, I should be very comfortable in this position,
because I still want to
go down, unless I still want to go, unless I still want to go, I can't make progress  I'll
feel like it's not possible, so I always know everything so I ignore other people
's voices, I think I tried, even if I failed even if
I'm not OK I at most change, in fact, at first is very suitable for
those things, that I do not know myself no ah, that do not
know it sometimes do not do it, then sometimes suddenly
tell people, what ten different kinds of
food with people, but sometimes what
?  It's because I haven't found my own path, that is, I
haven't thought, exactly where I want to focus on, to
I really think not, I really focus on the
exercise there, I should not be obsessed with whether I received money
ah.  That's because at that time I was teaching gama outside myself
, I would be with myself, next, but I'm charging
people money to teach, here I teach people for free, so what,
so like myself and myself
, right, but later I found that because there are
many people on the street, and then tell me their
benefit, that is, or they get the benefit of the
moment I feel
Money, so so I that think oh regardless, even my
students, he likes me to teach it, but if he has to
read my things on the Internet to learn it does not matter.  So I really
put everything out.  Do you have you have researched,
actually in the data is actually two groups of people from two different groups of people
, right?  Do you see him with a group of your online
or are looking for you to teach?  I think if online this is a group of
people who do not go out at all, that is a little more people, or they
may be after giving birth to a baby, that is simply no time to
go out, or simply usually is maybe students
or some moms, in fact, they will at most think,
oops,
I try to follow it, so it doesn't cost money, so it doesn't cost money
, so it's usually my own class
I really gave me money to teach actually another one of the
customers, so actually I think it's not really the same
group of people.  So I hear actually that you used to think think and
then do not act, and then found that in fact, bad to
worse then brought action for you so you act in the process
will not have any strategy
, or think clearly, or whether there is a frame, that is,
before you start any, I see you, inside you I just then I go to
you, and then you say now beg
Start to keep it so yes, yes yes.  Yeah
, so can you tell us what the plan actually looks
like?  No, because I'm thinking myself I've had
many, many sports videos before I, so but this
I think I have a baby this time after this I'm a lot lazy
, myself that has two public events, I'm suddenly
, I think my physical fitness is much worse, in either
way, because I never tried, because I
exercised for ten years I stopped doing so, but now
I actually want to save myself for a year
Head start.  Why can you give birth to children do not exercise,
can return to the body so sharp This is called
musclememory, because I used to
exercise too much, so I actually eat the old money this eat for a
while, I think I'm almost the end, then see the
beginning, that is, not us, start you feel
this, that is, I was no
[laughter]
before that but this
Kind of a bit muscular and seems to have lower body fat
, and then muscle a
good opportunity to go with you and everyone to start it
.  This actually this football country is very
content, or running a business, you have to
know how the audience feels, how the feeling under the buttocks
, I have to go
whether you have had this one such heart from the beginning.  Yes
.  Yeah, yeah, but I couldn't eat it before
, because I wasn't really [laughter] So I think this
series is because actually I would feel it.
However, there are many people who follow me to exercise, they may be stronger than me now.  It's
really difficult, that is, this group of people came in and I
started this thing, and then we really worked together to do this
, I think it's very passionate, do you understand, that
we feed, I'm really hard, I understand, I'm tired,
my one, but we have persisted
It was when Ncovid, you started, or
before covid when it was actually, I remember the
beginning when I was at that time it was the plateau period it, starting to
go, I do not know what the pursuit and I was a
little depressed at that time.  why  I don't know,
I don't know if you think YouTube is a
thing that can be done old, but for me it's not.
Even if YouTube can last for so many years,
I really do not know, but it does really have that
in the to keep running running running running running running running after it seems to create
this thing, that you, you can't actually n it, that
you can't stop will have.  A new pursuit.  Were you guys on
daily shift at that time?  Wow, is it daily shifts for your
channel? Not daily?  Follow no, I'll a week
.  a week.  So but a week there are a lot of sports videos
, because you have to keep thinking, because I'm not,
I'm not someone else's frame So, what if that is my colleagues who make videos
, everyone knows what my style of making videos is?  I
am never.  I also don't watch other people's movements,
nor do I set what I do at the beginning.  I was from the machine
, I started what I thought to do today.  Why is it like this
?  No ah, no plan, because the person is
, OK, because I just think I'm at home, how I'm going to
help myself lose weight, how I'm going to help myself in class,
I do that.  OK, so you
run your channel up to that point, it starts to
flatten as well.  I think flat is my own
mood very flat, that I myself would think what else can I
do?  I feel bored.  So after the
depression you think to get a
recovery.  It was someone someone looking for me first and so someone looking for
me said alas, let me fit with you, in fact, why is it
?  That's when I gave birth to my son like that, I on I
put on a pajamas is that brand, so then
he suddenly told me he said you know I finished
giving you after my whole site of pajamas, um.  Then he said
I have never tried any art or anything that
has this effect, then he told me, you must not
waste your influence, he said I better I go with you to
start a brand, so he is working in the factory, so at that time
he wanted to be with me, but later I left him
, because I do not want to do life with people, you and why
you like, why do you like, why
Firstly, and conflict, secondly I think even if I am quite a
sea relative, I will have my own ideas different from others, I
myself will think that the biggest problem with doing business with people is eh, you can
never benefit from a conflict of interest interests, if you this
company does not make money by yourself
Why did you carry so much?  There will be
a lot more, he won't talk about it.  You have
experienced trauma, so you have this idea or is it you all the way
I actually I think the person is very like to see others, there is a time that
I used to date a boyfriend, he and others folded
a restaurant, but I did not know, let those four people on
, that is what those called, stick eat stick, some money lost
that is, then I think next door
Things are really not fun, do not mess with it so, so I have asked
him, I said so actually I myself a real
business to how much money so, in fact, really
not much right, that I have this money in my mouth, why I have to go
with you?  Why why, right?  Actually I can't think
of the reason, so I told him, so then to later he
told me, so even if you do not do it with me, I do your factory
, that is, I help you to produce what you want to do
, so I think it's OK so, I started designing
, started designing the first clothes out first so, but then
I was
working on the website for a long time, working on it for six months.  You
do it all by yourself you say first alone that I find someone to do,
but I of course is water, my street is really do not know how many
times, I am constantly so is so falling, that is, at
first I have lost my own money, that is, for example, he told me to make a
website, very cheap, I charge you 100,000 dollars
, so I help you get it, oh.  I didn't know that I
found out that he was a middleman. He collected the nine dollars in the middle.
To be like this [laughter]?  Then I went to the
person who paid the dollar, I'm wrong you charged me five big bucks, you didn't follow
him and then told me how much money he gave me
, then I don't know how much he charged you.  It turns out that it is very difficult for you to depend on
one person to help you do some solving these IT
problems.  Because your salary means you have to take a holiday
, you have to sleep.  So what if he ಯ machine so what, I
am no one to help me.  But the person in the middle did not help you follow no
, I left already unlucky, moreover, so I'm
saying you do business no matter what, you think, you
plan to do whatever you want, actually you will,
because you will not be so beautiful, because you have not tried it, like our
life, that seems to have a lot of people will think I was
young to protect my children, that is, from harm.  But
I tell you, in fact, everyone is bound to get hurt, it depends
on whether you get hurt early or late, I want to say that you get hurt early better
than you get hurt late, just like I have to go to my own actually I
have to let others so quite, you understand, yes, that is I finished
, yes, accumulated, I still do not draw you understand I still
think it is better to continue to save this so much money, I go down
.  I at the same time has complained about my mother can not take pictures of it
huh the boss can not, crazy, and interested, wow
and screen, I first sell things when, because it is really
too good to sell, I want to say is out 12 times of the blank screen
gave 12 times, ah, such customers are more than hundreds of ah
, make a phone call, to refund one by one.  So you are
talking about following you have designed the finished year, engaged a
year after launch when too good to sell.  The
server can't put so many people, maybe
only 10 or 200,000 people rushed in at once, and then your goods
bought out within two hours, so but those two hours inside the people
are very want to buy, so tap tap tap, see the hundred screen
continue to tap tap tap, so he gave an example of the Visa
charge is still 12 times, the first up to 12
times, I returned like this ten times
Call him one by one and say sorry, I
called myself, that is, I think this trauma is so great, I think
the site is making me crazy, that is, I have not given up
the site yet, I continue to use until I heard a
friend go to give birth, he told me you do not have any more ារ time, he
said you quickly switch to it, you make such a
software is within 100,000 dollars
Get things done, you grew up 100,000 dollars, you turn better than your money
how much stop loss yeah no, then to
ū.  You are switching what switched to another, but you no longer do
I switched an
international is
so I'm better from life Although again earlier early listen to your
friend say the do it, do not do so many things that do not
[laughter]
so, but these, I think it is done, you ask me back do you
feel stupid?  I think it’s a learning
process.  The necessary process must go through, that is, I think these
spend that money, you think you do not deserve
ѓу you are really good, that is, in fact, everyone must go through it
.  Even if it’s not these things there must be
something else.  You used to be you as an actor, and you do the screen ah and so on
, in fact, you would not go to do profit without experience
.  It’s not really one that opens up your new world.  It
's totally you why you how this thing?  That is, you start your
team, how do you think about it? You are more deceived. You will
have shadows and shadows. You are you. How do you
approach this?  That is,
what is your learning in the middle?  I myself would think that it is all the way to hit it
, that is, sometimes you will think that feed, I hire a top student back
must be able to, but it turns out that is not the case.  I may you
understand this too.  It and doing things are two different things, that is, whether
a person is awake or not and his power is complete.  So you now
think if you have to hire a person, you mainly see
what, you have to you have not said two or three accurate if the plant then this
actually he does not have that force is OK, there is no such progress
.  That I now think yeah, that you mean the job interview
, the most important thing is that I already am right
, I see him myself, but I will first see him and I have
no content I tried to have seen some of it is straight
even Icontent did not dare to have this, that is,
looking at the phone.  Meet or
eh, there's GoogleMeet, but there are some very
strange people's, he talks a lot of questions and old, but I came back after I
hired him and I found, that is, for example, oh you help me with this
.  Oh, that's business.  Right? No,
that means it's already started, then he finished and he said I was done
.  That he won't help me think a step, nor
will he wonder if I'm my boss doesn't need to do this?  That
he just will it like a computer, like a
Google field Googlesearch like that
, that feed me ask you to find things he does his way to follow your
feelings, but he does not care behind the results actually want to achieve what
purpose.  He also does not care, that he in short I am doing what
you have to do, so he is this called dead study, that
you personally is not a thought of your own so, but I also have a yes
, maybe he is foreign, so he is not
really highly educated, he is every time maybe I told him
oh what you have to do, follow because feed me found what you want to do
other than OK, I think I also found  That he
would give me solid g, then he would do the whole thing for me
, then I would feel wow really different the feeling
, but I myself will feel that people are a good thing I still
think is the most difficult thing.  I've been learning lately, actually I've been starting a
business over the years, maybe learning it,
when I interview, I actually want to talk about it
, that is, our first meeting with him
here, he talks to me like that
I think this [laughter]
, I think this one should be a little what,
this channel, should be what, then all is a
little match but I think he's there
engyer I like that.
keepgoing, keepgoing
, follow after listening.  But actually I found that there are many agreed-upon
behaviors you should have when you meet, in fact, I think there are many
things that are not actually necessary.  Counter what you said out how,
whether he really pays attention to what your
channel to do, or maybe your
business, exactly what, in fact, that en if star
more important.  That is, is he tight on the content behind you
?  Just follow the procedure, like you just.  No, some are
really good, some are the most
to the phone, follow дээ you ask him things oh.  That's a thing.  I so
are you applying for a job of course?  [Laughter]
Because
wow, really it turns out that some people really feel like that, so but
I myself would find it difficult to manage people because one of them
comes with humanity so it changes how you communicate with him
, how do you make him comfortable, and then you let him know that you
are the boss, you can't be too nice with him, but
you can't bargain too much
How do you get him to gamble with other colleagues and then the two of them
can do it on their own to accomplish this, which is me, I
myself would think it's actually quite a big one Yes, for me to say
, that is at this stage speaking, I myself would think I'm the best
just don't care about so many people have so many people to me, that is not so
many people to call me to tell me what happened,
now you just need to send me a colleague
What's going on, OK, you go tell them, then I'll
ignore it.  That means how big your team is.  Not
very big, I used to be more people, so now I
shrink less and less, because there is AI, plus actually I
think really finished too much, that you really useful people,
actually you less, but he I would rather out more people to him,
that I wish we are doing what we do so and now
because my business has developed a lot of
outsourced, for example
Yeah, so it's a company, the physical store is another
company to help me, they have their own team, they
have fixed there, so what I need is my
admin part, that is myself maybe
I have several colleagues, one is responsible for things, one is responsible for
admin  It
's their assist, how to go so many
things, in fact, they asked me back how to do, in fact, they are we
instead I think villains, I myself
manage more comfortable, because I think
if you have too many different voices every day non-stop so with me
, I will be crazy.  Time constraints, in addition to watching
this, there are many highlights for us can not put in the frame If you want to
see, remember to click join abnormal headquarters member exclusive
here, this I guess is from, because you have many identities
, you have to be a mother and teach gama followed by a
channel, and have to engage in a business.
Found that all you are full-time
jobs, you as a mother you have a
full request timejob, how do you
manage your own time there is a moment that you really
can not, can no longer feel it.  I even before
doing influence here, that is, for example, my own
contact, in fact, some people feel good, I write myself
for in people I talk myself I negotiate the price I myself
experienced this.  Yes, I did my own things, I changed my own videos
for him, everything was my own, he found everything was me
, I got to this and rolled myself He
didn't have his left hand at that time, quite stylish, that is, I walked in alone
.  So but this I found to go
to a position, I think I personally is about to collapse
, because I will feel wow 24 hours I really not enough,
there are I gave birth to my children, wow, I do not have time to do my best
thing, already a day used up so, then I later
I found I really that you will have a moment you will be very big very
big very big is that you can not do enough that you can not do
well
, because of doctrine, yes, that he must not have done well enough
, he must not be able to talk to the customer, because it is not me
, I talk well.  To, now this I will, sometimes
I at the same time, you let me talk to him myself, because I have my own
set of ways to how to talk to the customers, we know what their
price is what I also know what I bring to him
so I say I think I can do this,
but this thing, I think because this is already selling the door to the
order, but once
Crush that stuff, I now that I have a good open, I am
all that my husband told me you are out of quantity for these colleagues
, you do not let others do things, you all do it yourself
so you hire them back to do what.  This is not
something your husband will tell you.  My husband I said I was cold again for
a while, I still can not let go, followed by slowly
I really feel can not, I do not let go of this I I can not do
content, I can not continue to go down the frame
so, I really let go, I let go one by one.
So I want to know, you have said Lord we will not say let go of it
, or there is a preceding sin order of it, you will you will choose what
first.  I will choose some of the latter things, that
is, for example, the Coffeesw website, they behind
and those factories that match, those goods, have voted
CS, those I that do not care about the things.  In short, pass
admin yeah, all yeah those things I, I used to be
very insistent, I do it myself, because I would think I have to be
with those customers is the most I have to have them have any complaints?  The
first thing must be me, they will go to mine every time
and tell me, so you think about every day when you keep having this
information, it actually affects your people, because you
will think I am really that bad, but in fact there may be
tens of thousands of people who buy you, but there may be a few
people, they are not satisfied with things, you will
because you are so infinitely enlarged  Now
even this thing I put out of it, that I think
not, I now no matter what he told me that ah you find me back to the
CS um you will help you solve.  Well I guess actually you say,
well I'm paused now, I let go, it sounds like it's
easy like that, but you in the middle of it means if it
's so easy to let go early done it, so
how do you go about this process eh show that means how do you go and
go back to OK at the same time eh eh, in the future this part of this will need to be added to you will
not be a lot?  Or what to do with
these situations?  At first
you will feel very annoyed, you will feel alas, hey I do it myself
less than five minutes to finish the answer, I have to teach you how but
you will find that actually this means those colleagues are very smart
, that is, you will because you say that one time he will write down your
answer, and then the next time because of form knowledge, every time some people's
questions are actually slowly
learning, in fact, he will learn slowly  It
became beyond it, because I do it, I'm not so professional yet
, I still give people the feeling that it's myself that feeds, okay this
should be OK so I didn't look at the numbers.  That is, if he
does, actually he does more finely, because I still I still
follow I went to do other things, I myself will think I did
very well actually not so, so actually this is not to slowly slowly slowly slowly slowly slowly
with yourself apart, you have to tell
yourself actually I really am not so, not everything is
known.  That there are some things I didn't turn out to be long, I hand over to
others.  That is, for example, I know that I am not a deep-thinking
person, I am not a person who deals with numbers nor a person who deals with
c or not an admin person, so these things
I let others so I part of I am responsible I am
responsible to think of a piece out, I think I have to shoot how I want to be a
person so, I continue to stay energy in this shot,
advantages how to design my clothes out, that I'm in this
Place I have to keep working hard like that.  You, have you ever calculated that it
is you who ordered something irrelevant, afterwards?  Pit you
every time.  A lot, I sometimes think I'm good as soon as I
think I'm not doing anything?  Is there anyone who says that
three hours, four hours and five hours a day in Hong Kong is counted? Actually, it doesn't count that way
.  Wow, glad you bought back so much time.  Yes buy,
and you really buy back, because you at the same time you are out of quantity to
them, but he out he is to help you to solve the problem, so so
I think these money I give very service, and actually I
myself will feel in this generation, in fact, I do not
need those working at the same time, they do not have an
office, I even cry for money.  We think first
you start a this, actually you need.  At
this moment, it's not up to him to tell you to blow you, to tell you
how strong your company is, not all this.  And I think the
first thing, you first is your is good your company to be
stable enough, you start from small does not matter, that is like I
started I actually my warehouse at home, I did not even have a warehouse no one cooperates
, did not do rent, and then I spend more money to develop
my products, to do good products, to put on my website
how to progress, and I put on  That is how to
give me some while and then ask them to
work within the range of clever, actually I spent this money out, but
actually I received a greater return, so I think I am not
afraid to let people know how much my business is, but I hope people are
constantly seeing the progress, I hope I can stand up, and
then I can up my own team, and then I can slowly I search slowly before I
do research
Last year you can comb right, yes I saw you say, wow first eight
digits right yeah that head first down to digits it has been an
amazing number actually I should say that, I was from the
beginning I was spending a relatively small amount of money, um, I was going to test the
water temperature, try the one.  So extremely limited, and then there
touched it and it went up.  Yeah, then I slowly
continued to invest in my business with the money I earned, so
I went non-stop to develop different products.
People used to be telling me that I was absolutely impossible to do business
because I was a very small person.  Such a person, that is,
I am not the one who will rush those people, I am not the one who does not have
, and then take all his own savings to do a business,
I am not the thing from these people.  I must see the one in front
, I have to see the road is going OK?I slowly walk
over.  Your day is mainly to put is to be a mother
, 40% to do a business ah how are you arranged?  I
myself is very difficult to take, because the look is what I want to do so
, my part I am one, that may be an influence of the film
so, I will go to help people shoot
advertising so, I myself have a Coffee
swag business, I have a mother, that is, there are
many different identities, is high, I
should focus on which side?  The sometimes think
wow, I seem to do too little, that I will see people rush
very important, no, I see people rush very important,
that I see people, wow, why can he
post so many videos in one day, why can he do so many things, why
can he still work with people to make this, that I rarely
feel so self  To
say the least, I first need to know now my own that is the it,
exactly what I value most so, I soon I
said OK at the same time, what I value most is.  Family money can't buy
her happiness, home can bring me happiness, I think this is
something I'm putting first as a mom now
.  Yeah.  Secondly I think it is my Coffee
swag, this is my second bb, I myself would
think of this as a practice.  I want to keep improving in this
area myself.  The third is that I might be making
videos, which is on YouTube, and
then in those commercials, those sporadic things, so that's what
I'm like.  Don’t you think it’s even more important?  Actually it's
quite important, because otherwise you become an eagle
, that is, you will keep hitting the glass like this, hit here,
hit and do, you will find that nothing has been done in the end
that is like who needs your time over there, you go over there and have to right
, so to speak.  Yes, but actually you find that you
didn't do one thing well, which is like I actually do as a mom
, that I stink all the time baby I cut the video all the time, I'm
here talking to my ads all the time about how to make the video, but
now you ask me, feed it, now there is a place that must
go to it we where you go first I go to my daughter is so
, that's me and myself.  do
you have many  Dno is
more because I guess that you ranked
priority means you need a lot of other things
.  Yes, yes, I do that means I, I am not going to
useless
supposed activities anymore.  Since when have you had this talk.  I,
I used to do this, I, I think we all know a lot of
responding, that is?  At that time I would often see some big
shots, that is, for example, your
boss's boss he would open the gas he would what so you would then
think wow, I know who who right I know who who
right seems very strong, right?  In fact, you know them does not mean that
others know them, in fact, even after you meet him you introduce
yourself, you are just one of the people at that event
.  And if you have no reason to use value to him, in fact,
he will not remember you after he communicates with you.  That is nothing back
, in fact, you find these things.  It's going to be something flipping,
OK? So but when I get to the end of the day when I do it myself, which is to be my own
body, or my own brand
, as long as it's a valuable person, other people will
come and find you because they think you're valuable.  Yeah.  But
if your value people come does not apply, in fact, it will
not arrive at all, if you need me one day, you will definitely want to
go in and touch coffee but I do not need to go to you that is
called
I do not care, you will not always care about me so I actually this one
thing I relate to you, because I am
in the network to survive it, we are in the network here to find the
people on the Internet
Well, that's risky.  Yes, you dare not feel to suffer at
risk.  I would think so, first of all, the person cut is not
different from your real person, that is, because I think the so-called
person cut this, is some people will think I seem to do the second
because
um so this thing can not be, that is, if you are a
not such a person, you choose to make yourself a person who wants to
see the cut will always break one day, because the
person cut is not you.
Protruding out, that is, when something happens and then you can no longer
do that to be angry when suddenly people will
fantasize, that is, no fantasies, so or at the end of the day
I myself will feel that I have no eyes never put myself that so-called
to do on the Internet do a person cut, but I
put my real side on the Internet so say, so but I
understand because I put people
While on the internet, when on YouTube they.
It was once twice three times, from the first time I know your
news I dislike you very much, I see what your father says like that
, so yeah maybe the first time is there is a
judgment like that to see my video to the second time the
third time, no right things really OK right.  Sigh, do it for a while that
really works, then began to slowly listen to me when
he found that feeding this girl is not what I think is
not the newspaper written so, not social
media so said, why is this, that is why
would be so big, so they found I want to know
more of this girl, why became my world, so
slowly entered his world
face, and then he found out to be friends with me, and then he
slowly discovered that being a street person I now my feeling, that is
you currently speaking, I will see your heart is very strong,
and you already seem to be because you know you are in a
network world when, in fact, you will always have a different voice, there
will be someone who likes you yeah does not like you yeah, follow you are now
snow is also very immune, you straight now is also immune
Is how is approach this one thing, that is,
when you are suffering after a game, for example, say back, then
you were told by TVB.  So how did you go about fighting
?  Or how you go about the situation of different sexual responsibilities
I want to know.  Actually, it's not just outside the ugly
words, but even their own family will leave and tell me he said
you better leave Hong Kong, which means you can't stay here anymore
.  How unbearable the situation was, it was because there was no money, no
money, no apprenticeship, and I was a girl, why this then
I would be that people really think I do that what
actually I really do not yeah, I really you now talk to me
until I was 80 years old in bed I told him, I did
not do anything inside, I did not do anything
I'm saying that I didn't teach that myself but there is no way to frame these
things, that you are already some people have taken it, that the
video is true, those send are true
.  They need to believe this to be true
Get a professional too, I've passed this time.
So I think wow, I draw back now again and say, actually, to be honest
, do I really
hurt my kids, because I have my kids, I have
my family, I need to need to protect, I don't need them to
go to this hurt anymore, I think even if it's what I go to explain it to them
, I don't need to explain it to anyone else, because I
know what my kids are like enough
.  Do you think it supports you to climb back out of the low period
?  What does essence energy and side energy look like, are there any available do
you think?  There are, but I myself will think I'm
war, OK? Yes, I'm not saying ah my
DNA says I'm war, he's saying I'm
IQ normal OK, but EQ is warri,
which means I'm a very strong person who resists stress.  What do you
think during that toughest period?  Essence energy helps you
as d, or energy helps you more.  Essence energy.
What is sperm energy?  It should be saying that I don't think about those negative quantities
, that is, why is my positive energy?  Because there were a lot of
people scolding me but actually there are many people who trust me
in emails, they are from different parts of the world, that is, at that time
I felt so big impact that I now
remember all the content, that is, every letter they remember
is telling me, yes, that there are really such people on the Internet
, I did not think there are these people on the Internet
I'm a chicken [ __ ] times the person, but that those people are an
emailsend for me to tell me, actually this
thing is a funny thing and it's your own thing you don't wear people
's things, I don't think how you do I think you have to cheer up
.  That these people in the words, at this moment
I will want to cry when I talk about it, because I think I am good, I think there is
really a kind of person in life is going to be low and you have no relationship with you
, even your family says you like that, they will
trust you like that, that is, you have to feel that I have to
say for you, I have to tell you that you are right, that is
Right for those people, that means I would think that way.  It's his
great energy.  And I see myself being over the top,
I have my PRcrisis.  That is, do you
think the energy helped you I was the energy helping me, but I
think I'm almost the same as you [laughter], I do think the energy is
OK, everyone has and trough feelings just energy
, I don't, but I don't think
you actually see a lot during that time.  I will see
who the people who care about me are, and what you just said that each person
sends one to actually I have it, but this cannot be
denied, is that actually I have a lot of, there are many people will think
I am very positive energy of so what point, but I was thinking
, how I can use these negatives should not be that we
face a different sound, how do we fight
I would describe it this way, you are going to go to these people you are on the
opposite side of him, but you have to tell him that you are sitting I too
, so this is a war
, I have commonlanguage with you
I have something to prove.  You have something to prove too, of course there
is one thing you have to prove, and you have to prove that it is
tied to your identity, I am not such a
person.  You bent me, actually the energy there is
very strong.  Yes, yes, yes it will take you
out of any difficult yeah how difficult things, you may have to OT
you waste your own time, or is simply done no less than others,
you can prove it, but it will you going.  Yes
, yes, why do you participate Yes, so but actually this one is
a motivation so, but this motivation is not because of
all the emotions of negativity.  But because you are not understood.
You are trying now I want to tell you what kind of person I am in
, I want to give you some positive energy, it should be said
, we want to give you some proof energy to tell you, in fact, the
world is not really as miserable as you think, or as
disgusting, that is, I would think so.  I have I have a very
ageless question for you.  Very not [laughter]
because actually you have suffered a lot of blows, you will have
many different periods you will have your difficulties to get over it so if that
is touchwood, Mori has 1 day to come
, and there is one, it will be a blow to you
Do you already have a stepbystep
way to deal with these things?  Would you say OK is coming again
?  The first step I have to do like this, is there a
framework for such a structure
I want to know.  I want to say that since that incident, I have
not let anything move.  Oh that
is whatever you think is some size is gar some
, maybe wronged me, I remember a while out of
what I still, how many points after still being covered
, I do not know what the hell.  He said that there is it, it seems to
be true, no one dared to help me find what I went to do for a while that is
because they think it is too negative so and so
, but these things for me, do not affect me at all
, because I would think that no matter how you say it
, it is not the fact of the matter, no matter how you
poof something out, sooner or later
Laugh and then get over it, so if you really I have done something again
then I go and I'm afraid, so I didn't, so what do I go to
?  On I really said in TVB, that is to leave, when
asked me to leave, in fact, I have begun to feel like life is like
catching a wonder, I myself will think so, I have
not put myself in, I instead drew out is
how I go to play this game.  I think life for
me is a game, money for me is
a spear, um, I myself will feel like I'm on the outside of the basin standing
, and then I'm here I catch this issue, so, but what I've never
thought about is not just avoidance, that I'm not
afraid either, that I think I have to stand upright You tell me at this moment, so
I'm
a person.  Where are you standing inside your pot now?
What's the next stand you think will be difficult for you?  Where is the
neck, so not admitting defeat?  Have you ever thought about this one thing to
this child will not open
think it, actually their own control of it, to the next generation when
I found that there are many things, it is not their own
control of it, that is, how do you go to mom you can love
this person so much, how he is out there treated and things happened
when, how exactly can you pull the body out of the real and then say how to
do the family or follow yourself
, I think the business of this is even harder than the business I do out there
[laughter]
Ha damn you that is such a small child, so naturally innocent
, such a cute child how should I go to tell him about this
, how should I go, sometimes I feel like I do more than that,
what should I do this boss?  That sometimes I
think this business is even harder, yeah do you think it's like
actually doing business and kids?  It's the same thing actually I'm at
home, that is what I'm responsible for, so how does theirs
work yeah, how, actually a lot of times have to ask me so
become they are an employee, I say so.  And this
employee was not fired.  There is no firing, follow [laughter]
stupid is ah is stupid so and so only depends on what, so and so
, but hopefully within their own ability so you so if
you face something said, then you are facing
escape from
me usually me, I am not right and not running away, I have no
feelings, maybe almost the same as you, because in fact, if I will still be affected by
negative comments for more than
ten years.  But I wonder, you need to know which kind
?  You know what offensive comments and frames are, you can
tell.  I think if there's actually an attack, I'll be able to tell
if it's a eh, what's that called sexual criticism.  If
there is a pretentious criticism, I will not jjud
judge him at the beginning.
In fact, it is very rare, I have
someone even I feel feed, such a high amount of gold when,
I will straight and reply back to thank him.  Yeah
, it's lucky you said back to the knowledge, yeah, for example, he
would say to me sometimes, "Feed, you're the host, you're always
interrupting people like that oh, is there really
this behavior look
f's first, maybe because I have a reason behind the bottom,
must need to deal with it like this may not be so, always the
biggest feelings the most or the most is yourself, in fact,
no matter how others discuss you, you think you in people's heart where
very heavy if, no, you only after that meal, because after
the meal that tea is
talking about you, then after, how do I look at
home?
onecareaboutyou, one
Yes, actually will not be depressed to the earth half a minute OK after I
experienced that, one of my quite big
learning this is that it turns out my past crisis
or some gaming or, it has become a part
of me um, it is a part of my life story Um
and I will not, instead, I see someone in the past I will
share or maybe you yourself
will share  When you
turn out, you can actually bring your own
lessons, you can share so that he does not have to experience you
such a heavy price, can be very happy the whole thing you
have learned it you finished after you have it, I say to
you, some things I really did bad why would get
so?
In fact, when I say this, I think I was able to
refraace turn out, but do not really understand
that time I understand, oh, yes, I now for example to help
me point I do content when, in fact, I
applied, I said those such
points out so, but is it with a people can take
away the model of me to say so
Will think, even not want to be a servant, but at least call a servant
worth it, that is worthy of him worth so and I think in that thing what
I learned is I see a lot of people you thought were but
turned out to be ghosts you see a lot of people who don't come to you
, those may not necessarily be your family but those people until now
, they are still around me, because I never
think that I am a friend
Friend, I can't see the real people, but I at that moment
I see a lot if you have a person around and is experiencing a
great difficulty like that, this is again single d
, [clear throat] Do you think if you as his friend
then how would you comfort him, I think if he really goes
through such a big is when,
I think I will be able to deal with him,
because I will actually be able to deal with him
No one is going to tell me anything, but I think what the person at this moment
needs most is not you to teach, nor is you telling him
what you should have done in the first place, or what you did wrong
, but you are by his side, if he really happens to this
, I won't say anything to him, and I wo
n't keep holding on to him with my face, but I
will still use my strength to listen to him
.
If tomorrow the world does not have a day then this will want to eat with which one
I think family, yes, to choose which one can not
, must a [laughter] together, I can not choose, it is
not possible, four men together can not die, must my
husband son my daughter, he
would rather sacrifice me
Friend, I will think I understand a kind of love I never
understood before, that I because I may we say a
child of people listen, feelings yes, yes, you later d
I have not felt, you said let me know first, sir
, you said I might give birth [laughter] No,
because there are many people will feel that feed me want less trouble
Feel it, that is your kind is you willing to sacrifice your own
play to take his life you are going to
do, that is like I gave birth to it, that is me, I will
feel that I used to love me so low, that will mean that
I think I am very full, but it turns out, to a
place, you look at two of their own children, you are going to know
if I died a day 2
Come, either take away your child, I would say no, you take
me away, I go away, so I think for human nature is selfish a kind of
born violated, that one is without love this
kind is
beyond, and they are to give me the meaning of survival is
so serious I itself is that I every day I earn money or I
did anything, I think I did not find the
end of it
This goal I yeah, is I think I go to work hard I go is to
give them a eh rolemodel, I am to give a
They gave me a goal of how to become a
better person, because I really want to
continue with them like this, that I myself will feel wow
, every time I talk about children I will want to cry, so but I
am really touched, myself to be a mom again, that is, I feel
very hard that I used to be a mom
Yeah, very obsessive self became so real now, that
I do not mind people think I am not okay do not mind what people think of me
, but I hope my children's family we are that is me we
ourselves are
happy, we do not need others to know our happiness so that
actually we have some members' questions, is to join
so many questions and what the market members will have the opportunity to decide
Or join the battle
, my Yogabrand was actually
not that many online Jia brands when I opened it, there is no
reference frame right, that you all
have to think for yourself [clear throat] Yeah, think for yourself when there are
other brands, but not that in a good
hit or like until now, really everywhere is the right time to
do exercise three so I don't
think so yet
righttiming
Those are not comfortable right so alg so what this became a lot I
have the opportunity to do the clothes I want to do, I will
have a lot of requests put into their own brand
, and then I want to do something I like out
, in this enthusiasm, so that's when it became have your
own brand out of the second question asked you two YouTube
oh, that you want to do uber
I want to do
.
[Laughter]
On the son
uber is not a job, I myself will feel
quite happy to do a his
inspiration, that is, because actually he
is saying I see my mother like this I very my mother, he thinks me
a lot, he thinks my channel is very
successful, that for a while I
want to stop I want to no longer shoot things, he told me mom, what do you do
not shoot things, I shoot you with you
Shoot it
He why he would want to be a youtuber, and not
he saw others, is because he saw my mother a so
successful, he thinks he thinks successful YouTube white
so, I told him, in fact, is not successful at all
, I think it is millions, in fact, this foreign country people are do not
know how many billions of followers so, but
he said, mom I think you
are a success, but
Yes I think I want to tell you, actually I think it's really not a
forever care, I think it should be said
, YouTube is your one channel to put your
things here, should it be a place, um, to
show your talent, if you don't have talent then you don't know.
No, I really, I think this is a good
platform, that is like TVB
, it used to be to rely on TV now is
YouTube, that is, if you are really
talented, or how you can rely on
YouTube or you want to release a song you can
release your own YouTube so, that is, so
I will explain to my children will
not encourage me
you? Actually I will take some, I would encourage, in fact, in
this coming era everyone that will be able to
benefit from having a
presence called socialmedia because it
can, there are many different benefits it will help you to
speed up your thinking, what kind of person you are, because you are
ready to see what kind of person you want to be, he can will
force you to think about this, secondly
It can be for you in work, or your own
life will bring all other benefits
, I see actually now, I heard some friends say he
worked in Iband so then he saw someone working this
one of his CV is about his own huge
following and
interview him that person will because of these
factors to consider that person frame, oh, you may also have
some real estate people now have seen the sell
Sun a network of very strong, that I see seems to be a
size so so but it will be, is
whether you are a cut Chinese people, your skills are what first you
have to think about you to put on it, so you have such a
socialmedia may be reversed will
ิก make you quickly to develop their own skill
set I have not yet
We live in this era, that we are witnessing and not
until now, that is like this previous identity, I am maybe your social status, your studies, now your identity instead is how many followers you will have on your IG, how many followers do you have on YouTube?  Yes
Exercise. He has a new show too, bye bye,
bye እ